I'm more pure than love.
I knew it before it was a nickname.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it.
I knew it before it was a nickname
I knew it
Hey, you look like you're in love with her
I can't do it
I'll conquer anyone in the night sky
No matter how many times I've walked away
I love music
The night you cried on my mountain
You who danced and watched me
That girl and this girl
And that girl and I are good friends
You're really neighbors with her
We're friends that spread out, and that's what counts
Wherever you go, people will tell you.
She and he and I...
"She and I are good friends.
And then it occurred to me that you were having a fight with her.
It's important that we're all friends
And that's okay, you start me off.
See you later.
I got there before the clock ran out.
She was the center of everyone's attention.
I don't know if she was ever able to move on
Maybe decades from now.
Stay strong, Lovelace.
I wish I could have been around then.
LOVE.
Maybe there's something we can talk about.
LOVE
If you let it into your heart...
I love that girl. I love that girl.
I didn't even know it was you.
Even your will is waiting for the light
I'm jumping out
Don't wanna see you say good
I'm gonna make a wish come true
That girl, this girl
That I didn't even know anymore
So that you and someone else can meet again
To the friends I'm connecting with, say good
I want to make a small wish come true
LOVE
With that girl and that girl
She and I are very close.
You are really that girl
A five-part love spreading
It's shining so brightly.
Quickly, love
With her and me
She and I are good friends.
I heard she was married to this girl
Even friends get entangled
That's okay, I'm in love too.
LOVE.
LOVE. LOVE.
LOVE
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
Don't want to be a
LOVE
Thank you for watching!
Hello! This time we have with us Rika Shimakura from Beyondz Subway and
and Nyukyo Shimoita from Angulum!
This time, we're going to show you the two of them, so please bear with us until the end.
Before Yukiho joined Angulum, they worked together in a project called "1 plus 1" in Takanawa.
We performed a song together called "By the time Takanawa Gateway Station is built" in a project called "1 plus 1" before Yukiho joined Angulum.
Do you remember that?
Of course I remember.
It's not often you get a chance to perform with your favorite senior, whom you admire so much, so I was really happy.
I was so happy to be able to perform with my favorite senior.
I was so happy and I was so excited that I actually got to meet him that I thought it was a dream.
I still remember how excited I was to actually meet him, as if it was a dream.
It's been a year and a half since then.
I really feel like Yukiho is a different person now than she was when she was a trainee.
I really feel that she's grown up a lot since she joined Angstrom.
I'm so happy to see her performance has matured so much.
I'm so happy!
Whenever I'm with Yukiho at Halo Project concert or Hina festival, she's always asking me
She always asks me if I want to take a picture with her.
I'm so happy that she kindly told me to do it like this.
Whenever I look back at the pictures, the distance between the pieces and the hearts is getting smaller and smaller, it makes me so happy.
Is that right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm really happy about that, and I really hope we can get to know each other better.
I'm not the type of person who can take the initiative, so...
Thank you very much.
You talk to me a lot, Yukiho, and that makes me really happy.
I'm glad.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you very much.
Now, please watch this video.
Here you go.
I'm Natsuyaki Kimiyabi.
I'm Akari Endo from JuiceJuice.
I'm going to do my best again this time.
What are you going to make this time?
Ishiyaki Bibimbap!
Do you like it?
Yes, I don't usually cook at all.
I can't cook at all.
But I'm going to learn a lot today.
Here it is...
Most of today's namul is like this.
Salt, sesame seeds and sesame oil
Sesame oil
That's almost all.
Where shall we start this time?
Yes, let's start with the carrot namul.
You can see a little bit of moisture coming out of the carrots.
Wipe off this moisture.
You can do it by tapping on the top.
You can wipe it off.
Can you see it's a little wilted?
That's right.
It's soft.
Do it up to this point.
Okay. Now, this is already salted, so all you need to do is
Sesame seeds, sesame seeds, sesame seeds.
You don't have to buy the non-blue anymore. Endless namul? Infinite carrots?
Yes, you can. Everything can be unlimited.
Let's have a taste.
I think you can do it with any vegetable.
I think it's a little crunchy.
How's the saltiness? Is it okay? I think it should be a little thin.
It's really good.
Shall we go?
Would you like some meat?
Have you ever grilled meat?
Yes, I've grilled meat.
The trick is, you put it down and you don't touch it.
It's better not to touch it while it's still on the table.
Spread it out as much as possible.
Let's try it again.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
A little bit, like half-burnt.
A little bit rare.
It's a little bit rare.
It's also cooked, and it's baked again with sauce.
I'd like to brown it.
I want it to be fragrant.
Are you planning to have a barbecue this summer? No?
No, but, uh, you know..,
A while ago, I was at, uh, JuiceJuice, TVB Malazine?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, um, we're going to have a barbecue together,
Oh, that's nice.
When we went to Okinawa on tour, we had a barbecue.
Oh, I see.
Even though it was raining.
It was raining. You did it even though it was raining?
Oh, really?
I think it's going to disappear.
There was a roof over the place, and there was some kind of cushiony place to sit,
It was a kind of place.
But it was like a rainstorm.
It was like a torrential downpour. Even though there was a roof, the wind came in. We all protected it like this.
Protecting the meat. We started with Halocon and other events.
It was my first time to do Halocon. It's the first time. It's the first time for the whole group to tour together. It's been four years.
It's been four years.
How do you like it? Is this your first time performing at Halocon? Yes, I am.
How? Well, there is a shuffle unit,
There is a shuffle unit, and I can do something that I don't do with the other members of Juice,
So, we mix with the seniors of the other groups,
So I will be able to mix with the senior members of other groups and perform songs other than those of Juice,
I also have to do my best to show my side,
I don't know how far I can go.
I don't know how far I can go, but as far as I can go is fine.
All of us have a song that breaks down in terms of the music,
That's right.
I don't have much experience,
Dancing up close with the fans.
That's right.
I'm dancing so hard right there, and the fans are right in front of me.
So, I have to be careful,
So it's quite a lot.
I have new experiences every day. It is completely different from what you usually do in your own group, isn't it? It is different, isn't it?
It is different. We don't get to hear the calls to other groups' songs. That's right.
I was surprised to hear such calls.
It was a fresh feeling. Yes, it was. The calls of my group, Juice, are also a little different from the usual. I see. There were many times when I felt that it was because fans from other groups were there.
The shuffle is also a bit of a challenge for the members, as they always wonder who they are going to be with. There are times when I wonder who I'm going to be with.
We watch each other at rehearsals.
We watch each other's rehearsals and try to improve our team.
We also try to steal from each other.
When we shuffle, it's a little different.
Also, I am representing JuiceJuice, so I don't want to embarrass myself.
I don't want to put them to shame.
Like you have to show your good side.
Yes, that's true.
But I'm glad you are enjoying it.
It's wonderful.
And the rice is cooked.
It's ready.
The pot is a little hot, you know.
I'll put it in, sir.
Please do.
And isn't it hot?
Is this place okay?
What a waste.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Sounds good.
Sizzle.
Here's the key, Miyabi-zu!
Bake the rice until it crackles.
If it becomes like this, okogi is ready.
After this, it's good.
After this, it's time to serve,
Please arrange the nori all over the rice.
Yes, I'll do that.
You want me to break it up? Nori.
As it is?
As it is.
And go through.
It's absolutely delicious.
Is it burnt?
I think so,
I tried to erase it once.
It turned black.
And the meat.
Wow, it sounds good.
Oh, that's nice.
Sounds good.
Okay, and then you need to make a little dent in the middle to put the eggs in.
Yes, quite a bun.
In chunks.
I like spicy food.
I do.
Yes, sir.
Wow, you did it!
It's done!
Kaede, you're done!
The bibimbap is ready!
So, how about it?
Oh, my gosh...
It's so amazing, it looks like she made it herself.
It's quite authentic, and the teacher brought this magnificent thing with him, so it turned out really well.
Then please try it.
Oh, it's good, isn't it? I like it curly, don't you?
Oh, it's done. It's done.
It's done! So beautiful! All right! Yes! Try it! Bon appétit!
Phew!
It's so good!
Great success!
The most delicious namul I've ever had!
I can't believe how easy it is to make namul!
It was so fast!
I wish I had three of them.
Sure, sure, sure.
You seem to like things with a bit of a quirk.
I want him to try all kinds of things.
That's the fun part.
That's for sure.
I'll give it a try.
I hope you'll continue to try your hand at cooking.
Yes, I will.
That's all for now, Hello Kitchen!
Good bye!
This is Rika Shimakura from Beyonce's Subway
Rika Shimakura of Beyons Subway and Yukyo Shimoita of Angelum are here with you on Haloste.
We're going to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So let's answer at a quick pace without thinking too much.
Yes, ma'am.
Yukiho, you recently celebrated your 18th birthday and held your first birthday event.
I was so nervous!
If you and I were to perform together again, which song would you like to perform together this time?
Oswing of Love by Beyonce.
What are you personally interested in right now?
The gym.
Is there anywhere you would like to go with Rika Shimakura?
Somewhere with a lot of nature.
What do you feel has changed the most in the last 3 months since you became 10 members of Angelum?
Unity in performance.
The question "Where would you like to go out with Rika Shimakura? This is a question I came up with.
Yukiho and I had a party once before.
Yes, we did.
That time we hung out in the city of Tokyo.
I wanted to go out again, so I asked.
Yes, we had a lot of fun after that.
We found that we both like places rich in nature.
I'd love to go out with you to a place with a beautiful view of the ocean or a night scene.
I'd love to go on an outing with you to a place with rich nature.
I'd like to hear more about your favorite food.
I would like to go out to eat delicious food with you.
And after 3 months as 10 Angelums
I feel that the most important thing that has changed is
Unity.
Yes, we are.
During the rehearsal of Rock in Japan Festival 2024
Ryo Kanguro said to me during the rehearsal
Ryo Kamiguro said to me at the rehearsal of Rock in Japan Festival 2024
Now that we've come to be united
I'm going to show my individuality and enjoy the performance
Let's enjoy the performance while expressing our individuality.
I think that's where the emotion
Everyone's motivation for performance increased.
I thought we were able to give a united performance.
This is the part that changed me a lot.
I hope we can continue to improve our performance in the fall tour.
Questions for Shimakura-san will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! STE (TV show)
Morning Musume。24「Something sentimental song
Now on sale
Tsubaki Factory New Single
Baby Spider Now Aun Sai
Chihayaburu September 11 release
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Shimakura-san a question.
Yes, I will do my best.
On August 7, Beyons celebrated the 5th anniversary of its major label debut.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you look back over the past five years?
I think it has gone by so fast and it has been a lot of fun.
What has changed the most in you over the past five years?
What has changed the most in you?
I've been very influenced by the beauty chart and have become kinder.
Shimakura-san is known for dinosaurs and insects.
What kind of children are you interested in these days?
Gold and stag beetles.
What is the key point of today's makeup?
Orange blush and lips.
What do you feel is the growth potential for Beyons?
The part that we create by ourselves.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure what to do.
What has changed the most in you over the past 5 years?
You have become kinder.
Became kinder? I feel that the Beyoncé has a lot of girls that I haven't met much in my life.
They're all very kind, but I think they care more than anyone else.
In this environment, I have been working for 5 years.
I've been working in such an environment for 5 years, so I'm naturally influenced by them.
I think that the atmosphere full of kind Beyoncé has permeated me as well.
Shimakura-san was always very kind to me, and he told me about what happened five years ago.
What do you feel is the growth potential of Beyoncé now?
I said something about the power to create by ourselves.
Beyoncé has a lot of talent, such as Honoka Kobayashi playing the piano and Momohime Human today.
Momohime can play the Human Beatbox, and
Minami Okamura can play DJ MeeMee, and so on.
We often incorporate our own special skills into our songs.
Many of them can play instruments and so on.
So we try to perform on our own.
I'd like to try a cappella or something like that more and more.
It's very nice!
Thank you very much.
I think it's great that hairdressers are so full of individuality.
My name is Yurika Asano, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture.
Music
I have always loved Morning Musume.
I used to listen to their songs and dance to them.
I was looking at social networking sites and saw an ad for Morning Musume.
I decided to be brave and send it to you.
I've been thinking about the issues I've been facing
and the differences between me and the other members.
and the good points of each member.
I've found the difference between me and the other members
But everyone helps me and practices with me.
I'm really happy to be able to get good at what I do.
My favorite music is "Give me love".
It was the song that Danbarl got the best performance in the assessment test.
I've been listening to it ever since. I'm good at dancing.
I learned cheerleading from the first to the third grade of elementary school and participated in competitions, so I am good at cheerleading.
I am addicted to hair and makeup. I enjoy curling my hair and changing my makeup every day to make it droop and bounce.
I used to learn figure skating. I did figure skating for about 2 years.
I did figure skating for about 2 years.
I took figure skating for about two years, and it trained my flexibility and jumping ability, which I use in my dancing now.
I like the sauce and the fact that it is kind of hard to eat because of the bones. I like hamsters.
My favorite sport is table tennis. I played table tennis from the third grade of elementary school to the third grade of junior high school.
I like the line here when I smile.
I think it's dark in the morning and gets more and more intense at night. Family, because I don't feel lonely when I'm with my family.
I'm with my family so I won't be lonely and they can help me. I want to be the best among the trainees.
I'll show you how soft my body is.
My problem is singing.
I can't sing very high.
I can't keep it steady.
I want to work on that a lot.
I sang and danced and sang so that I can make my debut.
I'm going to try my best to sing and dance so that I can make my debut.
I'll do my best to give an energetic performance.
I'll be happy if you watch my performance.
Sometimes I'm jealous. Sometimes I'm sexy when I kiss you again.
You're the one who says I have an impossible body. That's what makes you so attractive.
Sometimes Gieraci, you're dazzling again
Ah Tianbutsu-ish, love like a rose, Nawara-ne again
This time's Halo Pro trainee corner was Yurika Asano.
I met Yurika Asano for the first time when she performed at the Halo Pro trainee recital in March at BEYONES.
Yurika-chan has a very bookish atmosphere, and we have a lot in common.
Her bangs are kind of slicked back.
Sleek bangs.
I thought we had something in common, so I talked to her.
Yurika has "Rika" in her name.
I remember thinking we had that in common. She's cute.
She's cute. She's cute. She's got a warm, friendly vibe.
Yukiho, do you have any memorable moments from your days as a trainee?
I have a very memorable memory from the performance test.
It was a nerve-wracking experience to perform in front of the judges, but we were each other's rivals and friends, so the atmosphere at the school was great.
Yes.
The atmosphere at the school was not tense, but it was heartwarming to see the students praising each other's performance.
When I was a trainee at Halo Pro, I performed twice in the "I'm a talented singer" competition, but it wasn't the same as the usual recital in Paris.
It's not the same as a regular show.
Isn't it different from the usual showcase?
I was so nervous... because I never had a chance to perform by myself.
I never had a chance to perform by myself, so I have really good memories of it.
Please look forward to the next installment of "Halo Pro Interns Corner.
Rika Shimakura of Lions Subway and Yukiho Shimoita of Angulum present "Haloste".
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Asvega Altair has just finished!
This time we'd like to look back on some of the memorable scenes from the tour!
I, Rika Shimakura.
There was a shuffle corner in both Vega and Altair performances this time.
The contents of the performances were different.
First of all, in the Vega show, the members were divided according to their hometowns.
Yes.
In the Altair show, the members were divided into groups according to their colors.
Especially, the shuffle corner in Altair's show was divided by the members' color.
Everyone changed the color of their penlights to match the color of the members.
It had been a long time since I had seen the audience in the color of the members' colors.
It has been a long time since I saw such a scene, and there was a shuffle corner with the members' colors before,
We had had a member color shuffle before, but this was the first time in a very long time,
It had been a long time since we had a member color shuffle, and it was fun to perform among the colors of the members,
It was really fun to perform among the members in their colors, and it was a wonderful memory for me.
The view is so beautiful, isn't it?
The scene that left a strong impression on me was the shuffle corner of the Vega performance, where Ishida-san and Kawamura-san were singing together at the start line,
It was the kind of performance and facial expression that could only be achieved by the two of them, who are scheduled to graduate in the fall,
I was really moved,
I was very moved by their performance, and I felt sad and happy to see their performance,
I had mixed feelings of sadness and happiness to see their performance,
But when I saw the performance, I was filled with joy and it was a great memory for me.
It was really wonderful.
I am really glad that I was able to see it.
We have a fall tour coming up, so I would like to do my best to perform using what I learned from this summer tour.
Yes, I will do my best.
Let's all end on a high note with this song!
Iyi respeit
It's time to get around
I won't give up
My future
Still in a bad way
Of course
The place of the occasional
Dignity
Every day is a battle
Come on!
CHA!
Ah...
Yah...
Let's go a little further.
Oh...
Yah...
Don't take away the price.
Come on!
Dancing the night of
I won't forget again
The effect that helped me, now I can't stop.
Today, by nature
I've never been this strong.
I know why.
I've been so sick and tired of it.
It stopped tonight.
Bakhtiati.
It's weird.
I'm going on a trip.
I'm supposed to die.
I have to shine
My mouth will not fall
I'm not leaving you in anyone's hands.
Of course not.
In times like these
Let's let go and suck it up
All together
Jajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajaj
Oh, I can still spill the tune
No more just organizing the song
In the dance, there's a subtle seven in a row
I don't need so many no's in the dance
In the dance, this heart is crushed and pinched
It's coming out of me
I'm always getting cold on the way home
Tomorrow's waiting for me
Yay, yay, yay!
At the dance, they'll take a Seven like this
At the dance, I don't need this many no's...
Love love love go!
My heart is hot and it's glowing
My belly's getting warmer and warmer
It always gets cold on the way home
Tomorrow's waiting for me
Adieu!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for all your hard work.
Rika Shimokura from Beyons Subway and
Yukiho Shimokura of Beyons Subway and Yukiho Shimobita of Angulum are presenting Halo! Sta.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
This time, Yukiho and I were able to MC together for the first time.
I've always wanted to do it, so I was really happy too.
I was so happy!
We talked about the things we had talked about before.
Wow!
I remember how much fun we had.
I definitely want to play with you again. We promised to go out again. It was fun.
Yes, it was great! Here's an announcement!
Angulum's 10th anniversary tour 2024 autumn roots will start on September 21!
This will be Ms. Kawamura's last autumn tour.
We'll do our best and have a lot of fun!
And BEYONDZ concert tour 2024 autumn disco tic will start on September 29th!
And on October 12 and 19, BEYONDZ 5th anniversary event will be held!
We are very excited and looking forward to a lot of fun events this fall!
Please come and join us!
Hello! Project members will appear on the stage every week. Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Rika Shimokura from Beyons Subway and Nyukyo Shimoita from Angulum.
Thank you for watching!